[{"answer": "No, I haven't.", "docId": "130820pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "I mean, in all your time in police work, Captain Evans, have you ever come across anything quite so callous?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "VANS: You know, I really, as captain of investigations, we have a policy over here that, you know, I can't discuss what anybody's statement is, you know, if anybody discusses that, they are a little bit higher pay grade than me, but -- so I really can't go into the specifics of what any of them said, but one thing I can say about this group is they had the desire to be gangsters.", "docId": "130820pmt", "aSentId": 54, "question": "And final question for you, Captain Evans, just clarify for me, is it right that their explanation was simply that they were bored and they did it for fun?", "qSentId": 53}, {"answer": "There really has.", "docId": "130820pmt", "aSentId": 65, "question": "There's been widespread fury and distress in Australia over this, hasn't there?", "qSentId": 64}, {"answer": "Just for the record, Australia has had zero gun massacres since 1996 and the United States 80 people killed by guns every single day.", "docId": "130820pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "What is your reaction to what has happened here?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "Yes, I was leader of the Republican Regional Party equivalent, congressman equivalent, in a sense a Dick Cheney or Joe Biden equivalent, deputy prime minister, and I supported strongly John Winston out, and the initiatives for gun law reform and also former Vietnam veteran thanks to the USA, and I have and own guns, which CNN had footage of, as a matter of fact.", "docId": "130820pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "Let me just ask you, you were in a conservative government, weren't you, Mr. Fischer?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "Well, he was this kid that started actually at 7 years old at our club playing tee ball which is, you know, looked like a little league type program.", "docId": "130820pmt", "aSentId": 126, "question": "What kind of man was Christopher?", "qSentId": 125}, {"answer": "Look, look, Chris was such a level-headed kid that I think he knew his downfalls.", "docId": "130820pmt", "aSentId": 135, "question": "Did he like the idea of buying into the American dream?", "qSentId": 134}, {"answer": "Well, you know, what often characterized as juvenile violence is a senseless nature.", "docId": "130820pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "What do you make of this?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "Well, very much so.", "docId": "130820pmt", "aSentId": 163, "question": "How empowering is the gun to kids like this?", "qSentId": 162}, {"answer": "You know, it breaks my heart that a young man lost his life in such a senseless manner.", "docId": "130820pmt", "aSentId": 184, "question": "What do you have to say about it?", "qSentId": 183}, {"answer": "It's not a partisan issue, especially when there is a dead kid on the ground or -- or in the ground.", "docId": "130820pmt", "aSentId": 208, "question": "What is wrong with the argument in America that makes it so nonsensical?", "qSentId": 207}, {"answer": "Wow, that's a powerful question.", "docId": "130820pmt", "aSentId": 262, "question": "Lee, do you think America is more or less racist country since Barack Obama became president?", "qSentId": 261}, {"answer": "I think people just have a little more freedom to have this discussion and to say some of the things that they would normally not say in polite company.", "docId": "130820pmt", "aSentId": 279, "question": "What do you think, Star, to that central question of whether Barack Obama's ascent to the White House drew out more racism to America or it was always there and they just made the debate noisier?", "qSentId": 278}, {"answer": "They didn't throw race.", "docId": "130820pmt", "aSentId": 298, "question": "-- what was the difference really?", "qSentId": 297}, {"answer": "As we're walking away, I sit him down and he looks at his car and he goes, \"Is that my car on fire?\"", "docId": "130820pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "How fast after you pulling him out did it go up?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130820pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "Have you heard from Dick Van Dyke?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "But thank you both very much.", "docId": "130820pmt", "aSentId": 435, "question": "Yes, right?", "qSentId": 434}, {"answer": "You know, Piers, New York City is a city of immigrants, including immigrants from the Boston area.", "docId": "130820pmt", "aSentId": 455, "question": "A Red Sox fan -- Bill, how are you going to pull that off?", "qSentId": 454}, {"answer": "I've known Bill for 10-plus years.", "docId": "130820pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "So why not go with the glass ceiling and go with old Bill?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "Not so far.", "docId": "130820pmt", "aSentId": 475, "question": "The subtle charms of Anthony Weiner haven't -- haven't appealed to you?", "qSentId": 474}, {"answer": "Bill de Blasio, for a more fairer, more equitable, more just New York.", "docId": "130820pmt", "aSentId": 521, "question": "Cynthia, if you were doing a slogan for Bill, what would it be?", "qSentId": 520}, {"answer": "I think I prefer your daughter's line, Bill.", "docId": "130820pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "Is it long?", "qSentId": 524}, {"answer": "Yes, I think that's the best tag line I've ever heard.", "docId": "130820pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "Not a boring white guy?", "qSentId": 527}]